Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!
dynamic
Küá
Oh, uh, excuse me.
I'm not gonna hold up the signal.
What do you mean? It's a blind light.
I'll let you move on.
He bit me.
Featherboards!
I like it. - It's like New Year's.
Like batmint?
It's a traditional Japanese game.
You know, you put the seeds on this board.
You use this board to send the seeds flying.
A board version of batmint?
If you drop it, you lose.
Well, let's get to it.
Let's do it right away.
Let's make it a tournament.
Let's do our best.
Feather board! Oh!
Here we go.
Okay, then.
A little rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Seed rock, paper, scissors.
Seed rock, paper, scissors
rock, paper, scissors rock, paper, scissors rock, paper, scissors rock, scissors rock, paper, scissors rock
Poi, poi, poi.
Now absolutely
Par-par.
Then, gooper.
Go-per, go-per, go-per
Over par, extract, par, par, par.
I think I said goo.
Okay, okay. Okay, okay, okay.
All Jess!
Garmin.
Goo is 90%.
Katanning 宁 Different.
y aspects
k
a оже
This match? Shichi-Go-San-Kake This?
The 753-way match for The Point team.
Oh, my God, isn't it like this?
Shichi-Go-San-Kake Oh, that's good!
Hana-Rei Toyoeda eil Hana-Saya
Absolutely solutions
Can I use node's camera?
I'll definitely win!
Yay!
Nah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ah!
Boo-bah!
ah ah ah ah
voodoo
ah!
yes
OK, OK, OK
OK, not yet.
I'll take one more.
I'll do it again.
That's good.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's it.
There you go.
Ah.
No, I think we hit the jackpot.
I think we hit the jackpot, huh? Isn't it a jackpot?
2-2
2-2.
That's as far as you go.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm ahead of you.
No, no, no, no.
I'm going.
All right. All right.
Here we go.
Good game.
If I win, it's a performance.
It's like a performance that ends.
We're going to explode.
If it's too strong, it's not good enough.
No deuce, by the way.
Four points!
Match point!
Hey! Don't corner me!
Yes, sir!
I'm trying!
Ooh!
Hey!
Eighth place.
Yay!
Losing lineman
Easy win!
Oh! We won!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
That's it!
Reverse, reverse, reverse.
Let's go out-in! Let's go out and in.
Here we go!
Ten minutes...
What?
Out!
Now, now, put some pressure on it.
Okay, okay.
Out, out, out.
That's more like it. One pin.
Ready.
That's one less than I thought.
Oh!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
You're in.
Yes! Yes! That's good.
Nice cheese.
Okay, line up...
Oh, I don't see it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, I'm sorry.
It's getting dark out there.
I can't see.
This is a monster show, isn't it?
Huh! Huh! Huh! Huh!
Whoo!
Ha-ha-ha!
No, thank you.
Mr. Prince, you got teeth.
Mr. Tollefson.
I'll give you a little help.
Northern Positive N ⇨ como
I've had a baby for four hours.
I'm going to give you a centimeter.
I'm a very good person.
Aah!
Aaaaah!
Point 4-4 Point 4-4.
I'm in.
Yes, sir!
It's in!
It's a great game.
Last Last.
Well, then, you've got a good match coming up.
I'll take that as a yes, Kawakami-kun.
Ah!
With this one shot...
You want me to decide?
I'll decide.
Strong.
Ha-ha-ha!
Yeah!
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha!
No, goal pan bus!
Goal pan bus!
Oh, right.
Yah!
That's good.
Good, good, good.
Yay!
Good, good, good, good, good.
No way.
Next game.
Game three.
This is the best.
It's the last one.
Okay, now.
We're all a little nervous at the end.
Oh, you're not gonna be able to do everything.
Okay, let's start here.
Okay, here we are. Yes, here we are.
Well, first of all, first of all...
First of all...
Okay, which one?
No, I'll score.
Yes, sir.
I'm going all out. Oh!
I'll go all the way. Oh!
Let's go. No, no, no. Gun!
- Oh! Oh! Yeah! Yeah!
- What? Are you sure? Are you sure? Are you sure?
- Are you sure? Are you sure? Are you sure?
- Whoa! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
- That was a real hit, that was a real hit! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- Aah! Oh, yeah! Nice!
- Nice!
- Hey! Nice!
- Try to fight! That's probably the hardest part!
- Good luck with the serve!
Aah! Lanky!
Yeah!
That's fun!
Oh!
Are you in? Are you in?
What do we do?
Oh, no, it's not!
That means 3333.
Oh!
Hey, this!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you got any?
No?
Ah!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Ah!
Takasaki-san wins!
Goal, goal, goal!
That's good.
They're winning.
Seed vs...
Seed versus Masai.
It's practically a final already.
It was just a score.
Strong.
Oh, my God.
Good!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
That's great!
Come on!
Yeah, a little bit.
I've been over this line.
Oh! How's it going?
That's good.
That's better.
If it's there, it's out.
That's the last thing I want to find out.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, it's 30. 30.
That's what I said I'd do.
Because that's a weak seed.
Three.
Aah!
It's like a real, real final.
I'm in.
Oh!
I saw it.
Three.
I'm looking right at it.
Come on, observers. And now the observers.
Three.
Three of them traveling side by side.
I can't see them anymore.
What the hell is going on?
When do we go?
Whoa!
Oh! Oh, my God!
It's 3-3.
Aww.
All right.
Ah, ah, ah...
Game over.
You're under 19 years old.
Oh, my God, that's so scary.
Spo again.
So...
You're so lucky.
It's okay.
Okay, okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Seriously?
Oh, shit.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work.
Pachinko.
Pachinko
Click.
Yes, seed, here we go.
This one? This?
That was a good match.
Thank you. Thank you.
Good game.
Okay, what's next?
Next, both vs.
Nagashima.
We do this in the morning, don't we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We do it when the sun comes up, don't we?
Whoa.
Whoa!
Aah! That's good!
This is good.
Okay, great.
What do you think you're doing so well?
It's good.
Oh, my God!
That's great.
Is it weak?
Oh, that's good!
Oh, yeah!
That's great.
What?
Aah!
orgt 8 about
Grö buy.
Sand.
Oh...
premise
masters
Oh, no.
Just a little bit.
Ow, ow, ow.
Look at that. Watch this for a second.
Final game Koi-ed craft vs.
Ishida Ishida
Guy's a dame.
Oh, no.
If I win both of them, I've already won.
I see.
You're winning comfortably.
Let's go.
Good job, guys.
Good job.
Wow.
Can we go down closer?
What's that blinking thing?
You mean it just came on?
It's too strong.
That's good.
Good job, guys.
Just like boxing.
Yikes!
Stop being good.
Nice! Nice!
Oh!
No, no, no, no, it's already in.
It's in, it's in, it's in.
It's in our box.
It's in our box, it's in our box, it's in our box.
Shawya.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
That's why you have to be careful
Let's try a little harder
Let's try a little harder.
Mike.
I'm trying to keep it going.
Ahhh...
Nice item.
What? What?
That's not good.
I'm serious.
Ohhh...
All right, all right, all right.
Use that.
I'm in!
Now, sonically.
You just won sonically.
We're the winners.
We won!
What does the winner have to say?
I'm the number one box board in the local section.
Um, please tell me how you're feeling right now.
My feelings are on a green light.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
No, no, no, no.
You mean you're going to keep going like it's a green light.
You said you set a goal.
Congratulations, Takami.
You won the first Hakoban against Omitsu.
You're so good!
Hakoban is a game of... how many times can it go on?
That's the game, right?
It was a team game.
Even the first time, it's already solved.
No, there's a lot of people.
It's hard to say how many times it's gonna last.
Well, I won.
Green light.
Well, go back to the warm place for a bit.
I'll play a game I haven't played yet.
I'm off.
Let's go home.
Bye, bye, bye.
What?
Hey!Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Okay.
What's up?
Isn't it great?
Let's take it one plate at a time.
Until you miss.
Ooh!
Oh!
Yes!
Easy!